[
  {
    "question": "What's the correct way to create a variable named age with the value of 50?",
    "options": ["50 = age", "age 50", "age = 50", "age = \"50\""],
    "answer": "age = 50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the data type called that comes as a piece of text?",
    "options": ["text", "string", "word", "sentence"],
    "answer": "string"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will this code send to the screen?",
    "codeSnippet": "name = \"Joel\"<br />age = 31<br />print(name)",
    "options": ["name", "age", "31", "Joel"],
    "answer": "Joel"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will this code send to the screen?",
    "codeSnippet": "player = \"Ernest\"<br />score = 90<br />level = 20",
    "options": ["level", "Nothing / no message", "90", "20"],
    "answer": "Nothing / no message"
  },
  {
    "question": "What value will this code send to the screen?",
    "codeSnippet": "band = \"Beatles\"<br />song = \"Yesterday\"<br />song = \"Let it be\"<br />print(song)",
    "options": ["Let it be", "Yesterday", "song", "Beatles"],
    "answer": "Let it be"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's a bug in the code. Why?",
    "codeSnippet": "message = \"Debugging<br />print(message)",
    "options": [
      "The print statement is missing a parenthesis",
      "The hash symbol is missing for the comment",
      "The string value is missing a quotation mark",
      "There is nothing wrong"
    ],
    "answer": "The string value is missing a quotation mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which line contains the bug?",
    "codeSnippet": "band = \"Beatles\"<br />song = Yesterday<br />year = 1965<br />rating = 5",
    "options": ["1st line", "2nd line", "3rd line", "4th line"],
    "answer": "2nd line"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will this code display on the screen?",
    "codeSnippet": "score = 37<br />score = 38<br />#score = 15<br />print(score)",
    "options": ["37", "38", "15", "score"],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the result of the execution of this code?",
    "codeSnippet": "car_type = \"sedan\"<br />print(sedan)",
    "options": ["An error", "car_type", "sedan", "print"],
    "answer": "An error"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the code to output \"butterfly\" on the screen.",
    "codeSnippet": "a = \"fly\"<br />b = \"buter\"<br />c = \"butter\"",
    "options": ["print(c + a)", "print(a + c)", "print(b + a)", "print(a + b)"],
    "answer": "print(c + a)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the code to check and output the data type stored in the variable.",
    "codeSnippet": "movie = \"The Matrix\"<br />print(____(movie))",
    "options": ["type", "int", "str", "typeof"],
    "answer": "type"
  },
  {
    "question": "The division of two integers always produces...",
    "options": ["a string", "an integer", "a float", "a Boolean"],
    "answer": "a float"
  },
  {
    "question": "What data type is the variable \"is_adult\" storing?",
    "codeSnippet": "name = input()<br />age = int(input())<br />is_adult = True",
    "options": ["string", "integer", "float", "Boolean"],
    "answer": "Boolean"
  },
  {
    "question": "A traffic camera system detects speeding vehicles to automatically generate a ticket. What will this code output?",
    "codeSnippet": "speed = 65<br />ticket = speed > 70<br />print(ticket)",
    "options": ["False", "True", "An error", "Nothing"],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "An app recommends a movie if it has a rating higher than 70 and more than 5000 views. Complete the code to output True if those conditions are met.",
    "codeSnippet": "rating = 74<br />views = 5400<br /># Enter your code here",
    "options": [
      "print(rating > 70 and views < 5000)",
      "print(rating < 70 and views < 5000)",
      "print(rating > 70 and views > 5000)",
      "print(rating < 70 and views > 5000)"
    ],
    "answer": "print(rating > 70 and views > 5000)"
  }
]
